Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Music Center Operating Company files, 1949-2017
  - Ticket sales cash receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 294, Folder 1-4)
  - Ticket sales cash receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 295, Folder 1-5)
  - Performance statistics, 1974-1979 (Box 296, Folder 1-23)
  - Performance statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 297, Folder 1-12)
  - Performance statistics, 1977-1979 (Box 298, Folder 1-17)
  - Ticket sales and gate count reports, 1967-1974 (Box 299, Folder 1-12)
    This box also contains two tax status folders dated 1960-1972.
  - Performance statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 300, Folder 1-27)
  - Ticket information phone logs, 1974-1975 (Box 301, Folder 1-6)
  - Ticket office reports and sales statistics, 1972-1977 (Box 302, Folder 1-19)
  - Ticket sales reports, 1976-1978 (Box 303, Folder 1-13)
    This box also contains a Gala patron list and calendar folder dated 1976.
  - Purchase authorizations, 1968-1971 (Box 304, Folder 1-5)
  - Purchasing files, 1969-1971 (Box 305, Folder 1-7)
  - Purchasing files, 1966-1975 (Box 306, Folder 1-8)
    This box also contains Music Center Presentations (MCP) purchase orders.
  - Music Center Pavilion (MCP) purchase orders, 1973-1976 (Box 307, Folder 1-7)
  - Purchase orders, 1967-1982 (Box 308, Folder 1-11)
    This box also includes invoices and requisitions for building rental and maintenance.
  - Purchase orders, 1975-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1-8)
  - Center Theatre Group (CTG) financial records, 1969 (Box 310, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains records concerning the Minnesota Theatre Company.
  - Gate count reports, 1977-1978 (Box 311, Folder 1-7)
  - Performance statistics and gate count reports, 1977-1979 (Box 312, Folder 1-13)
  - Performance statistics and gate count reports, 1977-1979 (Box 313, Folder 1-13)
  - Performance statistics and gate count reports, 1978-1979 (Box 314, Folder 1-7)
    This box also contains ticket office reports.
  - Ticket office statements and financial records, 1960-1971 (Box 315, Folder 1-7)
  - MCP financial statements and invoices, 1961-1974 (Box 316, Folder 1-8)
  - Financial statements, 1974-1978 (Box 317, Folder 1-17)
  - Financial statements, 1975-1977 (Box 318, Folder 1-6)
  - MCP invoices, 1976-1977 (Box 319, Folder 1-7)
    This box also contains one Music Center Opera Association (MCOA) financial statements folder.
  - MCP invoices, 1969-1977 (Box 320, Folder 1-7)
    This box also contains ledger transmittals, accounts receivables, and MCOA San Francisco Opera advertising costs.
  - MCP, S-Z and cash receipts, 1976-1977 (Box 321, Folder 1-25)
  - MCP cash disbursements, 1976-1977 (Box 322, Folder 1-8)
  - MCP invoices and financial statements, 1976-1978 (Box 323, Folder 1-5)
  - MCP invoices and cash disbursements, 1978-1979 (Box 324, Folder 1-6)
  - MCP cash disbursements, 1978-1979 (Box 325, Folder 1-8)
  - MCP invoices and accounts receivables, 1977-1979 (Box 326, Folder 1-8)
  - MCP invoices, 1978-1979 (Box 327, Folder 1-7)
  - MCP invoices, 1978-1979 (Box 328, Folder 1-7)
  - MCP Cinco de Mayo files, 1974-1975 (Box 329, Folder 1-3)
  - MCP The Royal Ballet files, 1977-1978 (Box 330, Folder 1-11)
  - MCP Stars of the Royal Danish Ballet, 1979 (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
  - MCP Stars of the Royal Danish Ballet, 1979 (Box 332, Folder 1-2)
  - MCP The Royal Ballet files, 1979 (Box 333, Folder 1-4)
  - Fred Harvey operating statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 334, Folder 1-9)
  - Fred Harvey operating statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 335, Folder 1-11)
  - Fred Harvey operating statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 336, Folder 1-10)
  - Fred Harvey operating statistics and sales tally sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 337, Folder 1-12)
  - Fred Harvey sales tally sheets, 1977 (Box 338, Folder 1-6)
  - Restaurant concessions records, 1962-1971 (Box 339, Folder 1-8)
  - MCP vouchers and budget, 1981-1982 (Box 340, Folder 1-29)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1961-1965 (Box 341, Folder 1-3)
    This box also contains Theatre and Forum Lease Co. Change Orders dated 1965-1967.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1966-1970 (Box 342, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 343, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 344, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 345, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
  - Operating Committee Minutes, 1972-1986 (Box 347, Folder 1-7)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1986-1991 (Box 348, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1992-1994 (Box 349, Folder 1-4)
    This box also contains a Long Range Planning binder dated 1989 February 7.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1994-1999 (Box 350, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1964-1969 (Box 351, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 352, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 353, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 354, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1977-1980 (Box 355, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 356, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 357, Folder 1-3)
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 358, Folder 1-3)
    The Performing Arts Council Board of Governors changed its name to The Music Center Board of Governors on June 23, 1986 as documented in the Volume 24 Minutes.
  - Performing Arts Council Board of Governors Minutes, 1964-1980 (Box 359, Folder 1-9)
    This box also contains Board of Governors biographies, committee files, and two folders concerning the Music Center for the Performing Arts Academy dated 1969-1998.
  - The Music Center Board of Governors Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 360, Folder 1-5)
    This box also contains Performing Arts Council Executive Council and Executive Committee binders dated 1978-1982.
  - The Music Center Executive Committee binder, 1983-1987 (Box 361, Folder 1-6)
  - The Music Center Board of Governors Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 362, Folder 1-5)
    This box also contains Executive Committee Minutes dated 1991-1993.
  - The Music Center Board of Governors binders, 1992-1996 (Box 363, Folder 1-5)
    This box contains Executive Committee Minutes dated 1992-1993.
  - Associated Presentations Board of Directors Minutes, 1979-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 364, Folder 1-4)
  - Long Range Planning Committee Binder, 1986-1990 (Box 365, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains two Five Year Financial Outlook folders dated 1989 May 16 and a Board of Governors Campaign Year binder dated 1989-1991.
  - Executive Committee Campaign Year binder, 1989-1991 (Box 366, Folder 1-5)
    This box also contains Board of Governors Executive Committee Minutes dated 1993-1995 and Board of Governors Minutes dated 1994.
  - The Music Center Board of Governors Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 367, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains a Board of Governors Executive Committee folder dated 1997 and a Board Member information folder dated 1964-1993.
  - The Music Center Board of Governors Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 368, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains Board of Governors Executive Committee Minutes dated 1996-1998.
  - The Music Center Board of Governors Minutes, 1997-1999 (Box 369, Folder 1-5)
    This box also contains Board of Governors Executive Committee Minutes and a Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles County Merger Notebook for MCOC Board.
  - MCOC and TMC closing binder, 1999 (Box 370, Folder 1-4)
    This box also contains a Walt Disney Concert Hall Authorization book and The Music Center (TMC) and Resident Companies Fundraising Program binders dated 1992.
  - Strategic Planning DIscussion binders, 1992-1996 (Box 371, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains The Music Center, Inc. Executive Committee Minutes dated 1998-1999 and The Founders folders dated 1998.
  - The Music Center, Inc. Board of Governors Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 372, Folder 1-8)
    This box also contains Board Review and Nominating Committee Minutes dated 1994 and 1996 and The Raise Summit binder dated 2001.
  - Board Review and Nominating Committee Minutes, 1996-1998 (Box 373, Folder 1-14)
    This box also contains Board of Overseers reports dated 1990-1993.
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1991-1994 (Box 374, Folder 1-20)
    This box also contains a folder of correspondence concerning the Ahmanson Theatre reconfiguration and a Board retreat folder.
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 375, Folder 1-18)
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 1-6)
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 377, Folder 1-7)
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1999 (Box 378, Folder 1-7)
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Minutes, 1999 (Box 379, Folder 1-17)
    This box also contains Executive Committee Minutes dated 1993-1999.
  - The Music Center of Los Angeles County Board of Governors Committee files, 1993-1999 (Box 380, Folder 1-13)
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1966-1999 (Box 381, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains Center Theatre Group to The W.M. Keck Foundation Annual Report. Folder 7 contains one 3.5 inch floppy disk labeled "Chandler, Mrs. Norman."
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1979-1999 (Box 382, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains The Founders League Bylaws to The Founders historic documents.
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1963-1999 (Box 383, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains Founders League Articles of Incorporation to Korn/Ferry International. Folder 4 contains one 3.5 inch floppy disk.
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1998-1999 (Box 384, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains Lincoln Center to MCOC.
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1993-1999 (Box 385, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains Music Center Education Division to Reorganization.
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1987-1999 (Box 386, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains MCOC Merger to Spotlight Rights Issue.
  - Board of Governors subject files, 1996-1999 (Box 387, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains Thelonious Monk Jazz Institute to Volunteer Coordinating Council. This box also contains MCOC By-Law changes and disclosure forms dated 1964-1998.
  - Board of Governors files, 1997-1998 (Box 388, Folder 1-16)
    This box contains rosters, photographs, biographies, and expenses. Folder 9 contains one 3.5 inch floppy disk labeled "Fair, Jeremy G."
  - Joanne Kozberg's files, 1997-1999 (Box 389, Folder 1-15)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
    Folders 10-15 contain the following VHSs: Ruth Laredo Concerts with Commentary: Live from The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Eddy Awards: Eddy Tribute Video, An Introduction to Music Center Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles County, Walt Disney Concert Hall: Los Angeles Coverage, and Walt Disney Concert Hall: KABC, KCAL, KCOP.
  - Chairman's expense reports, 1996-1999 (Box 390, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains Joanne Kozberg's 1999 chronological file.
  - Stephen Rountree's files, 1989-1999 (Box 391, Folder 1-8)
  - Stephen Rountree's files, 1995-1999 (Box 392, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains folders labeled "Ahmanson photographs" to "Board members." This box also contains Board of Governors binders.
  - Board files, 1970-1999 (Box 393, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains folders labeled "Martin Bernheimer" to "Board of Governors Chairman."
  - Board files, 1985-2013 (Box 394, Folder 1-13)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Digital and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
    This box contains folders labeled "Deborah Borda" to "James Conlon." Folders 10-15 contain the following VHSs: Ruth Laredo Concerts with Commentary: Live from The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Eddy Awards: Eddy Tribute Video, An Introduction to Music Center Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles County, Walt Disney Concert Hall: Los Angeles Coverage, and Walt Disney Concert Hall: KABC, KCAL, KCOP. Folder 10 contains one CD labeled "Collar and Bow Groundbreaking 2005 June 29 Gary Leonard Photographer."
  - Board files, 1964-2007 (Box 395, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains folders labeled "Dorothy Chandler press clippings" to "Fountains." Folder 13 contains two CDs labeled "John Emerson Portraits by Howard Pasamanick."
  - Board files, 1964-2006 (Box 396, Folder 1-20)
    This box contains folders labeled "Frank Gehry" to "Personalities." Folder 3 contains one CD labeled "Julio's Archives Shots 2001 April by Howard Pasamanick." Folder 9 contains one CD labeled "The Music Center Kendall's Event 2003 December 6 by Howard Pasamanick." Folder 11 contains two CDs labeled "The Music Center Kozberg Party 2002 November." Folder 16 contains one CD labeled "Music Center Images 2006."
  - Board files, 1980-2007 (Box 397, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains folders labeled "Plaza photographs" to "Severns photography."
  - Board files, 1980-2005 (Box 398, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains folders labeled "William Severns biography" to "Andrea Van de Kamp." The Severns folder contains his oral history transcript.
  - Board files, 1991-2001 (Box 399, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains folders labeled "Esther Wachtell" to "Heritage State of the Arts." Folder 11 contains one CD labeled "Taper Photographs" and one CD labeled "Taper interiors (Rothschild)."
  - Board files, 1964-2006 (Box 400, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains folders labeled "Pavilion dedication photographs and slides" to "Wachtell Shortfall controversy."
  - Board files, 1964-1991 (Box 401, Folder 1-20)
    This box contains folders labeled "Wachtell Shortfall controversy" to "Ahmanson from DWP."
  - Complex and events files, 1964-1997 (Box 402, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains folders labeled Ahmanson interior photographs, a Music Center history and description article, Music Center What You See and What You Get booklets, and MCOC articles.
  - Complex and events files, 1991-2008 (Box 403, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains photographs of the Pavilion, Mark Taper Forum, and Pavilion art works. Folder 5 contains one DVD labeled "Architect: Rios Clementi Hale, Job: Mark Taper Forum by Tom Bonner Photography" and one DVD labeled "Mark Taper Forum Civic Celebration 2008 July 29 by Tom Bonner."
  - Complex and events files, 1988-2008 (Box 404, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains Music Center slides and Shining Stars Tribute photographs. Folder 3 contains two CDs labeled "Shining Stars" and folder 4 contains three CDs labeled "Shining Stars."
  - Complex and events files, 2002-2007 (Box 405, Folder 1-8)
    Folder 4 contains one CD labeled Bowl photographs Mrs. Chandler project Rothschild, two CDs labeled Ahmanson Founders Room 5, one CD labeled Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, one DVD labeled Music Center stills, one CD labeled Disc C 7 images, one CD labeled Parties in Plaza, one CD labeled MC Plaza. Folder 5 contains two CDs labeled Grand Avenue Festival by Gary Leonard, one CD labeled Bow Tie Groundbreaking by Gary Leonard. Folder 6 contains three CDs labeled Grand Avenue Family Festival photographs and one Family Festival DVD. Folder 7 contains one CD labeled Music Center Art Database. Folder 8 contains three CDs labeled Ahmanson Founders Room 5.
  - Complex and events files, 1997-2005 (Box 406, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains Music Center photographs, negatives, and slides. Folder 1 "Center Photographs" contains five CDs. Folder 2 contains one CD labeled "Blue by Peter Alexander."
  - Complex photographs, circa 1962-2000 (Box 407, Folder 1-20)
  - Complex photographs, circa 1960s (Box 408, Folder 1-21)
  - Complex photographs, 1964-1971 (Box 409, Folder 1-10)
    This box also contains Master Calendars for the Mark Taper Forum, Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, and Ahmanson Theatre.
  - Master calendars, 1971-1974 (Box 410, Folder 1-8)
  - Master calendars, 1974-1977 (Box 411, Folder 1-7)
  - Master calendars, 1977-1980 (Box 412, Folder 1-7)
  - Master calendars, 1980-1983 (Box 413, Folder 1-6)
  - Master calendars, 1983-1985 (Box 414, Folder 1-5)
  - Master calendars, 1986-1989 (Box 415, Folder 1-4)
  - Master calendars, 1990-1993 (Box 416, Folder 1-7)
  - Master Calendars, 1994-1997 (Box 417, Folder 1-4)
  - Master Calendars, 1998-2001 (Box 418, Folder 1-5)
  - Master Calendars, 2002-2003 (Box 419, Folder 1-6)
    This box also contains Calendars of Attractions for the public dated 1965-1972.
  - Calendar of Attractions, 1975-1986 (Box 420, Folder 1-8)
  - Events Calendars, 1987-2009 (Box 421, Folder 1-8)
  - Music Center photographs, 1960-1969 (Box 422, Folder 1-66)
    This box contains complex construction and aerial view photographs.
  - Music Center photographs, 1963-1964 (Box 423, Folder 1-91)
    This box contains Pavilion construction photographs and complex negatives.
  - Music Center photographs, 1964-1988 (Box 424, Folder 1-70)
    This box contains Pavilion photographs.
  - Music Center photographs, 1964-1965 (Box 425, Folder 1-86)
    This box contains Pavilion, Mark Taper Forum, and Ahmanson Theatre photographs.
  - Music Center photographs, 1964-1984 (Box 426, Folder 1-66)
    This box contains Pavilion, Mark Taper Forum, Ahmanson Theatre, Plaza, Jacques Lipchitz Peace on Earth sculpture, and fountains photographs.
  - Music Center slides, 1987-1988 (Box 427, Folder 1-10)
  - Music Center photographs, 1962-1964 (Box 428, Folder 1-95)
    This box contains architectural sketches and Music Center agreement signing photographs.
  - Music Center photographs, circa 1970-1974 (Box 429, Folder 1-58)
    This box contains photographs of Charlton Heston, Armand Deutsch, Walt Disney and others. This box also contains Lease events photograph files for Adaptation/Next-American Ballet Theatre dated 1969-1999.
  - Lease events photographs, 1972, 1976 (Box 430, Folder 1-115)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Ballet Theatre" to "Ahman." Folders 23-73 comprise the Linda Simon photograph collection of American Ballet Theatre at the Music Center.
  - Lease events photographs, 1969-1975 (Box 431, Folder 1-86)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Dance Currents Rug Concerts" to "Josephine Baker."
  - Lease events photographs, 1972-1979 (Box 432, Folder 1-72)
    This box contains folders labeled "Victor Borge" to "Ella Fitzgerald."
  - Lease events photographs, 1969-1978 (Box 433, Folder 1-72)
    This box contains folders labeled "Roberta Flack" to "Nana Mouskouri."
  - Lease events photographs, 1973-1988 (Box 434, Folder 1-24)
    This box contains folders labeled "My One and Only" to "Phantom of the Opera."
  - Lease events photographs, 1972-1978 (Box 435, Folder 1-46)
    This box contains folders labeled "Rabelais" to "Royal Ballet."
  - Lease events photographs, 1978-1979 (Box 436, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains Royal Ballet photographs.
  - Lease events photographs, 1968-1979 (Box 437, Folder 1-24)
    This box contains folders labeled "Royal Ballet" to "Segovia."
  - Lease events photographs, 1969-1979 (Box 438, Folder 1-82)
    This box contains folders labeled "Rudolf Serkin" to "Theatre Ballet of San Francisco."
  - Lease events photographs, 1970-1979 (Box 439, Folder 1-24)
    This box contains folders labeled "Trinidad Tripoli Steel Band" to "Glenn Yarbarough." This box also contains a Lease event files alphabetic list of major lease events to Alvin Ailey Dance Theater, dated 1964-2006.
  - Lease events, 1973-2013 (Box 440, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains folders labeled "Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater" to "All Southern California High School Honor Choir and Honor Orchestra."
  - Lease events, 1968-2005 (Box 441, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains folders labeled "Steve Allen" to "American Ballet Theatre."
  - Lease events, 1975-1977 (Box 442, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Ballet Theatre."
  - Lease events, 1978-1991 (Box 443, Folder 1-11)
  - Lease events, 1996-2016 (Box 444, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Ballet Theatre." Folder 11 contains five Romeo and Juliet DVDs.
  - Lease events, 1965-2006 (Box 445, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Folk Ballet" to "American Youth Symphony."
  - Lease events, 1991-2001 (Box 446, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Youth Symphony."
  - Lease events, 1965-2003 (Box 447, Folder 1-23)
    This box contains folders labeled "American Youth Symphony" to "Hanna Aroni."
  - Lease events, 1965-2015 (Box 448, Folder 1-24)
    This box contains folders labeled "Claudio Arrau" to "Ballet Folklorico de Mexico de Amalia Hernández."
  - Lease events, 1971-2014 (Box 449, Folder 1-17)
    This box contains folders labeled "Ballet Folklorico de Mexico" to "Belding Awards."
  - Lease events, 1970-2006 (Box 450, Folder 1-22)
    This box contains folders labeled "George Benson" to "Bravo Awards." Folder 20 contains one Bravo Awards 2006 DVD.
  - Lease events, 1964-2014 (Box 451, Folder 1-22)
    This box contains folders labeled "Bravo Awards" to "Bureau of Music (City of L.A.)."
  - Lease events, 1966-2009 (Box 452, Folder 1-19)
    This box contains folders labeled "Bureau of Music (City of L.A.)" to "California Restaurant Association Educational Foundation Hall of Fame Gala."
  - Lease events, 1973-2007 (Box 453, Folder 1-34)
    This box contains folders labeled "California School of Professional Psychology" to "Circle of Friends Concerning Women." Folder 15 contains two Chandler Children's Festival 2003 audiocassettes.
  - Lease events, 1973-2016 (Box 454, Folder 1-26)
    This box contains folders labeled "City of Angels High School" to "Complexions."
  - Lease events, 1966-2009 (Box 455, Folder 1-33)
    This box contains folders labeled "Ray Conniff" to "Sammy Davis, Jr."
  - Lease events, 1969-2003 (Box 456, Folder 1-19)
    This box contains folders labeled "Lex de Azevedo's 'Gloria'" to "Distinguished Artist Award."
  - Lease events, 1965-2013 (Box 457, Folder 1-18)
    This box contains folders labeled "Jeane Dixon" to "Education Guild."
  - Lease events, 1965-2012 (Box 458, Folder 1-20)
    This box contains folders labeled "Eifman Ballet" to "Explororama Film Series."
  - Lease events, 1967-2016 (Box 459, Folder 1-22)
    This box contains folders labeled "Exxopulis" to "Four Governors (Zocalo)." Folder 18 contains one Fly to the Sky DVD. Folder 22 contains two Four Governors CDs.
  - Lease events, 1965-2009 (Box 460, Folder 1-32)
    This box contains folders labeled "Malcolm Frager" to "Global Pop Hugues Aufray."
  - Lease events, 1970-2007 (Box 461, Folder 1-18)
    This box contains folders labeled "A Global Triptych" to "Al Green." Folder 4 contains four Grand Ave Festival by Gary Leonard CDs. Folder 5 contains one Grand Avenue Project CD. Folder 12 contains one Les Grands Ballet Canadiens de Montreal DVD.
  - Lease events, 1968-2011 (Box 462, Folder 1-30)
    This box contains folders labeled "Green Valley High School Madrigal/Chamber Singers" to "Heritage Salutes." Folder 30 contains three Heritage Party CDs.
  - Lease events, 1975-2003 (Box 463, Folder 1-26)
    This box contains folders labeled "Heritage Salutes" to "Freddie Hubbard." Folder 13 contains one Music Center Holiday Sing-A-Long CD.
  - Lease events, 1969-2005 (Box 464, Folder 1-37)